#### Contact

jobicray@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jobicray (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Charge Nurse

Continuous Renal Replacement Therapy

Rotoprone Pronation Therapy

## Languages

Tagalog (Limited Working)
Spanish (Limited Working)
English (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Basic Life Support
Advanced Cardiac Life Support
CCRN

## Honors-Awards

2018 National Magnet Nurse of the Year for Empirical Outcomes

Daisy Awardee

2018 Registered Nurse Practice Award

2019 IHI Daisy Award for Extraordinary Nurses Honoree

2019 Baptist Health South Florida System Nurse of the Year

# Jobic Ray Butao

Patient Care Supervisor at Baptist Health South Florida Miami, Florida

## Summary

I am a Registered Nurse, currently working in the ICU of West Kendall Baptist Hospital as a Patient Care Supervisor. I attained my Bachelor's degree from Chamberlain College of Nursing (May 2015). I have experience in administration, conducting research, managing, teaching and clinical patient care.

I aim to achieve excellence in whatever I do through hard work, dedication and good planning. My challenge is always to aim for a high degree of proficiency. I am passionate about people, service, faith and extending this to those in the community.

# Experience

Baptist Health South Florida 6 years

Patient Care Supervisor February 2020 - Present (5 months)

West Kendall Baptist Hospital

Clinical Nurse Educator
October 2019 - February 2020 (5 months)
West Kendall Baptist Hospital

1

#### Critical Care Nurse

June 2015 - October 2019 (4 years 5 months)

West Kendall Baptist Hospital

Clinical staff nurse at West Kendall Baptist Hospital's Intensive Care Unit. We are a 12 bed unit that tends to high acuity cases, specializing in pulmonary and renal disease processes.

### Unit Secretary

July 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 2 months)

**Baptist Hospital of Miami** 

I tend to the admissions and discharges of the Orthopedic Unit. I take care of organizing the charts, documentation and physician/nurse orders and forms.

Page 1 of 2

I also tend to the phone lines and navigate the traffic between physicians, nurses, family and patient personal calls. We are also in charge of the call lights, supply stock, and stations.

Mercy Hospital
Critical Care Nurse
August 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 1 month)
Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

Clinical staff in the Cardiovascular Surgical Intensive Care Unit.

Worship Jesus Fellowship
Administrative Assistant
March 2014 - August 2015 (1 year 6 months)
10478 NW 31ST Terrace Doral, Florida 33172

Answering calls, managing church website, assisting the pastor and board of directors with office tasks such as filing, bill paying, check writing, and organization.

Forever 21 Sales Associate November 2013 - July 2014 (9 months)

Customer service, sales floor management, money management, and floor set changes.

## Education

Chamberlain University

Master of Science in Nursing, Clinical Nurse Leader · (2019 - 2020)

Chamberlain University

Bachelor's Degree, Bachelors of Science in Nursing · (2013 - 2015)

Florida International University

Associate of Arts (A.A.), Pre-Nursing Studies · (2010 - 2012)